{
    "translations": {
      "en": {
        "q2": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"How do we prove that a language is regular?<br/>We have a number of approaches in our toolbox.",
          "description": "Select these approaches.",
          "answer": ["Build a DFA.", "Build a NFA.", "Write a regular expression.", "Write a regular grammar.", "Start with known regular languages and apply operations known to be closed for regular languages."],
          "choices": ["Build a DFA.", "Build a NFA.", "Write a regular expression.", "Write a regular grammar.", "Start with known regular languages and apply operations known to be closed for regular languages."]
        },
        "q3": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Given so many tools for creating a regular language, are there languages that are not regular?",
          "description": "are there languages that are not regular?",
          "answer": "Yes",
          "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
        },
        "q4": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Let’s start with some basic questions. First, if a language $L$ is finite, is $L$ regular?",
          "description": "What do you think?",
          "answer": "Yes! All finite languages are regular.",
          "choices": ["Yes! All finite languages are regular.", "No"]
        },
        "q7": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Let’s start with some basic questions. Second, if a language $L$ is infinite, is $L$ regular?",
          "description": "What do you think?",
          "answer": "Maybe",
          "choices": ["Yes! All infinite languages are regular.", "No", "Maybe"]
        },
        "q8": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Infinite languages might be regular and might not be regular.",
          "description": "For example. $L_1 = \\{a^nb^m | n > 0, m > 0 \\}$, is it infinite language?",
          "answer": "Yes",
          "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
        },
        "q9": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Infinite languages might be regular and might not be regular.",
          "description": "For example. $L_1 = \\{a^nb^m | n > 0, m > 0 \\}$, is it regular?",
          "answer": "Yes, the RegEx is $aa^*bb^*$",
          "choices": ["Yes, the RegEx is $aa^*bb^*$", "No"]
        },
        "q10": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Infinite languages might be regular and might not be regular.",
          "description": "For example. $L_2 = \\{a^nb^n | n > 0 \\}$, is it infinite language?",
          "answer": "Yes",
          "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
        },
        "q11": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Infinite languages might be regular and might not be regular.",
          "description": "For example. $L_2 = \\{a^nb^n | n > 0 \\}$, Do we need to memorize anything to accept any string in this language?",
          "answer": "Yes",
          "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
        },
        "q12": {
          "type": "true/false",
          "question":"Infinite languages might be regular and might not be regular.",
          "description": "For example. $L_2 = \\{a^nb^n | n > 0 \\}$, [T|F] We need to remember the number of $a$'s to find the same number of $b$'s.",
          "answer": "True",
          "choices": []
        },
        "q13": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Infinite languages might be regular and might not be regular.",
          "description": "For example. $L_2 = \\{a^nb^n | n > 0 \\}$, What is the memory NFAs have?",
          "answer": "They only remember the current state",
          "choices": ["Infinite memory", "They only remember the current state"]
        },
        "q15": {
          "type": "true/false",
          "question":"Infinite languages might be regular and might not be regular.",
          "description": "[T|F]This means that we can not find an NFA to accept $L_2 = \\{a^nb^n | n > 0 \\}$?",
          "answer": "True",
          "choices": []
        },
        "q16": {
          "type": "select",
          "question":"Infinite languages might be regular and might not be regular.",
          "description": "Is $L_2 = \\{a^nb^n | n > 0 \\}$ regular?",
          "answer": "No",
          "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
        }
      }
    }
  }
    